

Spulber Ioan-Alexandru

Computer Engineering

Brasov, 500439, Romania 0729933229 <u>alexspulber291@gmail.com</u>

Date / Place of birth 07.05.2001, Romania

Nationality

Romanian

Driving license

Yes

S	ki	lls	

Teamwork

Adaptability

Fast Learner

Ability to Multitask

Computer Skills

Ability to Work in a Team

Effective Time Management

Detail Oriented

Catia V5

Matlab/Simulink

ADAMS

Unity

Arduino

Python

ROS

Profile

Currently I am a Robotics student, at the Faculty of Electrical Engineering, 4th year of study, I am interested in engineering as a whole pack, ranging from neural networks, data science, ROS, CATIA, finite element analysis, to embedded engineering, full-stack programming etc.

https://github.com/SpAlex01

So far my experience comes from my projects and some internships.

Some of my projects:

- XY plotter that can play tic-tac-toe (Nema17 stepper motors, opency, python)
- 6DOF robot made in unity, with a neural network that helps the robot's effector touch a random generated point (unity, C#)
- Ball and beam PID controlled system(matlab, arduino)
- Gearbox made in CATIA
- Kinematic, dynamic and structural analysis of a boat trailer made in Simcenter 3D
- Rotation Translation robot made with MATLAB and Simulink
- · Audio-Source separation Unet Neural Network
- Gazetracking and drowsiness driver detection
- ROS Pick-And-Place robot using Yolov5

Employment History

Agent in cadrul ITSG, Universitatea Transilvania, Brasov

December 2022 - Present

IT student group, aka ITSG, is a group of students that are passionate about IT and have the task to resolve and clarify IT questions/problems throughout the whole university, ranging from PC problems, all the way to networking and server problems. I currently work here as an agent, which means I resolve IT-wise tickets issued by university employees/students/professors.

Operator, Autoliv, Brasov

November 2022 - January 2023

Logistics, Somfy Romania, Brasov

Linux				
С				
Data Analytics	5			
Languages				
English				
Romanian				

Hobbies

As hobbyes, I enjoy calisthenics very much, I like going outdoors and enjoying the nature, people, animals. I love the automotive area, especially offroad trucks/cars.

Also I currently am in a pilot school, where I am learning to fly gliders, the no-motor aircrafts, which I enjoy very much, and in the feature I would like to learn to ride horses.

May 2021 — June 2022

Internships

Finite-Element Method Analysis Scholar, Siemens Industry Software, Brasov

July 2023 — August 2023

It was a 4 week bootcamp, where the first 2 weeks were dedicated to learning the software, Simcenter 3D, a CAE software built for engineering simulations. We had motion trainings, dynamic trainings and FEM trainings, trainings that we needed at our final project, a team-project where my team had to study the deformations and von Mises stress of specific parts of a boat trailer.

The main challange was idealizing the CAD of the trailer, applying the constraints, joints, then applying the real forces where it was needed and study the final results and present them to a jury.

Devian Learning School, IBM, Brasov

June 2021 — August 2022

Here I learned Linux basics, how to protect a domain, working with certificates, accounts, users etc.

PLC scholar, Caditec

August 2022 — September 2022

Education

Matematica-Informatica, Liceul Grigore Antipa Brasov, Brasov

September 2016 — June 2020

Robotica, University "Transilvany" of Brasov, Brasov

October 2020

Student in Robotics in the electrical engineering department of UNITBV, 3rd year of study, currently with scholarship.